[{"answer": "I thought I was screaming --", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 24, "question": "An old man sitting on his ass?", "qSentId": 23}, {"answer": "Well, I'm 50.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "Or is it fraught with pitfalls and potholes?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "You know, it really is, because when I do standup, you're your own boss.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "Did you find as you get more famous and successful, being very honest and candid is problematic?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "You know, it's interesting because as a child growing up, and a lot of our great sitcoms come from adaptations of British shows.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "Do you find a constant conflict between those two roles?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "You know, I -- I like the show.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "Do you mind all of the attention that comes with such a swap?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "I'm afraid it was, yes.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "Was that me?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "You know, there were things that he said that I was not appropriate to people of my own color.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "Like what?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "Which I found disingenuous from somebody else.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "I think when you understand the material, you understand it.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "What did he mean by that, do you think?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "I have no idea.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "I don't -- you know, I don't know if competition is the right word.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "I mean, is he much more competitive than people realize, do you think?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "Do you think he sees you as a threat potentially?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "Well, if you ask me personally -- I know you didn't ask me -- who I thought should have been the host of the \"Tonight Show\", I think when Johnny Carson left, which I was fortunate enough to do that show with him in 1991, I thought the heir apparent would have been David Letterman.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "Isn't that the Holy Grail still?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "And you still believe that?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "Well, you know, personally, in my opinion, I don't think that \"The Tonight Show\" should have been offered to Jay -- to Conan O'Brien.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "How did you feel when Conan and Jay had their huge split?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "Do you do that?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "We're going to go outside the family and get somebody to help.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "You're going to breastfeed him?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "You know what, I do.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "Do you miss doing the show?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "And they both left before you were like 10 or 11 years old?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "But neither your parents nor your grandmother ever told you they loved you?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "That's an interesting question.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Do you like to be loved by lots of people now, in the way that you are?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "You know, if I was a can at the store, if I was a can of soup at the store, I would have a dent in me and I would be in that basket that they have at the end of the hall, at the end of the aisle that says these are 99 cents, everything in the can.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Do you feel damaged by your upbringing still?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "Yes, I remember.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "Did you remember that and how it made you feel?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "At least she was there.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "At least she was there, right?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "She did not.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "So she may not have been perfect by a long way and clearly wasn't able of expressing the kind of love and care that you might have wanted, but she didn't abandon you, right?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "I keep her in my dressing room.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "Where do you keep her?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "Do you really?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "I think that I wasted a -- I think that I wasted a lot of time not seeing her when I should've spent more time with her.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "And when you look at her, what do you think?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "I wish that I would've told her that there was nobody that loved her more or anybody that would've protected her more than me.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Is there anything you wished you'd said to her that you never got the chance to?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Yes, I think she did.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "Despite the fact that she wouldn't show that -- do you think she knew?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "You know, I -- on Father's Day this year, my friend -- a friend of mine, we'd just come back into town.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "Do you ever think about your parents, or are they just something that you blanked out, really?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "You know, Ann -- Ann was great.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "What did marriage bring you, given all that you'd been through?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "The kidney thing created an awareness of kidney disease, but also of a wife giving a gift to her husband, which I've run into a lot of people that have done that.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "How much do you think was unfair?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "It's a problem for me.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "Well, I'm 50, so I think I'm fraught with pitfalls and pot holes.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "Or is it fraught with pitfalls and potholes?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "I --", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "So, what are you going to do?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "I'm going to take Tylenol PMs and sleep a lot.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "What's going to happen?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "It's been a little difficult for her.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "How's your daughter been through the whole divorce?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "She was 14, and she's 15 now.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "She was 15?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "I don't think I -- you know, I always wanted a father.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "Do you think you're a good father?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "For her, yes, because it's my only unconditional love.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "ORGAN: Do you think you have it in you to be the father you'd like to be?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "We have Obama, we'll have Lobama.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "Would you like to be?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "This is a great city, and it's my city.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "Why would you seek public office?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "-- bonding the city back.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "What do you care about most?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "Well, I'm disappointed with his performance as far as immigration goes.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "Would that be fair?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "I will go further north.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "I would leave the United States of America.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "You would literally leave the country?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "OPEZ: You know, I like my politicians to actually have a political background, to be politically -- to know politics, to actually have inherited something from working in the political world.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "Why would you be so drastic?", "qSentId": 618}, {"answer": "Well, she's --", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "How does she resonate with people?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "I think it's scary to me now politically that -- and addressing the immigration thing, again, with Carlos Santana is that we feel like whether we're here -- there are more people in the United States here legally than illegally, but there is a service provided that no one else wants to do.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "Do you find it quite scary?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "You know, you have to make us feel like we're important in the United States.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "And what is the simple best way of getting somewhere to resolving this?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "I would win -- no.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 661, "question": "Have you got bigger political aspirations?", "qSentId": 660}, {"answer": "It's an embarrassment of riches.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "I kissed a Smurf and I liked it?", "qSentId": 668}, {"answer": "Yes, you said it, absolutely, of course!", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 674, "question": "Right, Smurfs?", "qSentId": 673}, {"answer": "I did not see any of them.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "But you didn't actually get to see any of them, right, in the filming?", "qSentId": 679}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 715, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 714}, {"answer": "I like the fact that I did something that I never imagined that I would do and something I told my friends I was going to do, whether I believed it or not.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 717, "question": "Do you like being famous or is it quite restricting now?", "qSentId": 716}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 721, "question": "I'm going to come over a final break and ask you if you could relive one moment in your life, again, what would it be?", "qSentId": 720}, {"answer": "I would say that without Sandra Bullock, I would not have had an opportunity to -- in the last 10 years, to have the career that I've had.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 735, "question": "She sort of found you, didn't she?", "qSentId": 734}, {"answer": "On occasion we talk, yes.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 739, "question": "And do you still stay close to her?", "qSentId": 738}, {"answer": "No, she's a good woman and she had -- has always been very loving to everybody, very fair to everybody.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 746, "question": "She just didn't deserve that, did she?", "qSentId": 745}, {"answer": "You know, I -- it's interesting, because it's -- I was a -- I was a huge Freddie Prinze fan, of \"Chico and the Man.\"", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 754, "question": "If you could relive one moment again, what would it be?", "qSentId": 753}, {"answer": "You know, the one thing that I believe that nothing was ever going to be given to me, and nothing was ever going to be easy.", "docId": "110730pmt", "aSentId": 766, "question": "What have you really learned about yourself?", "qSentId": 765}]